hello Jeff thank you for joining us
你好杰夫，谢谢你加入我们
today thank you very much yes good
今天非常感谢你，很好
morning good afternoon good evening
早上好下午好晚上
depending on where you are
取决于你在哪里
my name is Jeff Brown and as Andre said
我的名字叫杰夫·布朗，正如安德烈所说
I'm one of the cofounders of the Grails
我是Grails的联合创始人之一
framework and in the Grails practice
框架和Grails实践
lead here at OSI Act which Damon
在达蒙的OSI法案中领导
Congress said is the OCI are the
国会表示OCI是
stewards of the Grails framework and
Grails框架的管家和
have been for some time now I've been
我已经有一段时间了
involved in the girls projects and
参与了女孩项目，
pretty much the very beginning I had
我几乎一开始就有
felt some grand Murphy and I co-authored
感到有些墨菲，我与人合着
a couple of the definitive guide to
几个明确的指南
Grails books you can see a Twitter
Grails的书你可以看到一个Twitter
handle there an email address so you
处理一个电子邮件地址，以便您
know how to get to get a hold of me if
知道如何得到我的控制
you need anything I am based here in st.
您需要我在圣保罗这里居住的任何物品
Louis Missouri in the United States
路易斯·密苏里州在美国
where we of course have the have the
我们当然有
Gateway Arch this is this is not my
Gateway Arch这不是我的
family it's just a picture of them here
家人，这只是他们的照片
in st. Louis we have one of the great
在圣路易斯，我们拥有伟大的
things about st. Louis is we've got the
关于圣事路易斯是我们有
st. Louis Cardinals here and the
圣路易斯·红雀队在这里和
Cardinals as most of you probably know
你们大多数人都知道的红衣主教
are one of the most successful and above
是最成功的项目之一
professional baseball teams in history
历史上的职业棒球队
so I encourage you if you're coming to
所以我鼓励你，如果你来
st. Louis hit us up and we can take you
圣路易斯打了我们，我们可以带您
to a ball game have some dinner drinks
参加一场球赛，喝点晚餐
there's a lot of great stuff to see in
有很多很棒的东西要看
st. Louis but reach out to us if you're
圣路易斯，但如果您愿意，请与我们联系
going to be in the area in the time here
将会在这里的时间在该地区
at OC eyewear we're a distributed
在OC眼镜，我们是分布式的
company distributed all over the world
公司分布在世界各地
but our headquarters is in st. Louis
但是我们的总部在圣路易
we've been around since the mid 90s and
自90年代中期以来，我们一直存在
been an open source company the entire
整个都是开源公司
time we've got more than 140 engineers
那时我们有140多名工程师
on the team here many of them have
在这里的团队中，许多人都有
advanced degrees in their field and we
他们所在领域的高级学位，我们
cover a whole lot of ground with a
用一个覆盖整个地面
software engineering practice an
软件工程实践与
industrial Internet of Things practice
工业物联网实践
we do a whole lot of work around open
我们围绕开放做了很多工作
source and training has been a big part
来源和培训已占很大比重
of OC eyes business since the very
自从
beginning and certainly we offer a lot
开始，当然我们提供了很多
of training around groovy and grails and
关于groovy和grails的培训，以及
Gradle and really all the technologies
Gradle和所有技术
and in the whole groovy ecosystem so
在整个常规生态系统中
definitely reach out let us know
一定要联系我们
whatever it is we can do to help you out
我们能做些什么来帮助您
Denis back so specifically related to
丹尼斯回来如此特别相关
grills so oh she has been the home to
烤，所以哦，她一直是
Grail since 2015 and we're having great
自2015年以来一直保持领先地位，我们一直在努力
success with the technology we're
我们所拥有的技术取得成功
investing heavily and growing the team
大量投资并发展团队
to help accelerate the development work
帮助加快开发工作
so in the first couple years and in the
所以在头几年和
last couple years we've been releasing
最近几年我们一直在发布
about 30 releases per year which is
每年大约30个发布
great little debate we've only been able
很少有辩论，我们只能
to do that by growing the team and
通过发展团队和
investing as I said in the technology
就像我在技术上所说的那样进行投资
we're really broadening the technologies
我们真的在扩展技术
reach and that comes in a number of
触及范围
forms we're expanding born to talk to a
我们正在扩展的形式与某人交谈
lots of different data bases and
许多不同的数据库和
introducing new profiles or interacting
引入新的个人资料或进行互动
with lots of other technologies like
还有很多其他技术，例如
react and angular and we're but the
反应和有角度，我们只是
bottom line there is that we're
最重要的是，我们
investing heavily in the technology and
在技​​术上投入大量资金，
moving it forward just as quickly as we
像我们一样快地前进
can and that the practice is having
可以，而且实践正在
great success and I expect nothing but
取得了巨大的成功，我只希望
more of the same in the future so as you
将来与您一样
said reach out to us if there's anything
说有什么可以联系我们
at all we can do to help you out and we
我们竭尽所能帮助您，我们
would love to talk to you so I want to
很想和你说话，所以我想
get right into the technical details are
正确了解技术细节是
the heart of the presentation this is a
演讲的重点是
high level agenda what what I want to
高层次的议程我​​想要什么
cover so we've got the introductions out
封面，所以我们有介绍
of the way and so as I said Braille
就像我说的盲文
system is the home of OCI and has been
系统是OCI的所在地，并且已经
for for quite a while now and we're
现在已经有一段时间了，我们
having great success but what I want to
取得了巨大的成功，但我想
talk about today is I want to talk about
今天说的就是我想说的
the relationship between IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA之间的关系
and in Grails 3 I'll discuss a little
在Grails 3中，我将讨论一些
bit of a history about how we got to
关于我们如何去的一点历史
where we are today and really what I
我们今天在哪里，真的是我
want to get into is some differences
想进入是一些差异
between Grails 2 and rails 3
在Grails 2和rails 3之间
specifically that relates to
特别是与
productivity in the in the IDE or kinds
IDE中的生产率或种类
of capabilities the IDE can provide and
IDE可以提供的功能以及
and so there's some details about some
所以这里有一些细节
critical change or significant changes
重大变化或重大变化
that we made from rails to the rails 3
我们从铁轨到铁轨3
there's some of those details that
有一些细节，
specifically relate to IDE functionality
特别与IDE功能有关
and there's some confusion around a lot
周围有些混乱
of that in the community and what I want
在社区中，我想要什么
do is press into some of the
要做的就是压入一些
capabilities that intelligent has that
具有智能的功能
specifically relates to building grills
特别涉及建筑烤架
three applications demonstrate some of
三个应用程序演示了一些
that and and clarify some some
并澄清一些
misconceptions around the relationship
对关系的误解
between the two part of that has to do
在这两个部分之间
with the community addition of
随着社区的增加
intelligence is the ultimate addition so
智力是最终的补充，所以
I'm going to talk a little bit about
我要谈一点
that that's that's a particular area
那就是那个特定区域
where there's some confusion in the
那里有些混乱
community about how those two relate to
关于这两个之间的关系的社区
doing rails 3 development so there's
做rails 3开发，所以有
some demos and I'll demonstrate some
一些演示，我将演示一些
tips and tricks and things that I use
技巧和窍门以及我使用的东西
every day when I'm doing development in
我每天在做开发时
the ice and and I think you'll find that
冰，我想你会发现
interesting and helpful and then the end
有趣和乐于助人，然后结束
of the line we'll we'll have time for
我们将有时间
Q&amp;A and I'll address just as much as I
问答，我将尽我所能
can around beneath that so drills 3 has
可以在下面钻，所以演习3有
been has been around for more than 2
已经存在超过2
years
年份
we're coming up on about two and a half
我们大约要两个半
years now since rails 3 was released and
自Rails 3发布以来已经有很多年了，
grills 3 was a major iteration a major
格栅3是主要版本，主要是
step forward for the framework or
向前迈进框架或
significant changes in the framework and
框架的重大变化
one of them has to do with the build
其中之一与构建有关
system and that's this specifically
系统，就是这样
relates to capabilities in the IDE and
与IDE中的功能有关，并且
I'm going to demonstrate some of this
我将示范其中的一些
but in grills 2 we had in Gray's wedding
但在烤架2中，我们参加了格雷的婚礼
Grails - we had our own build system and
Grails-我们有自己的构建系统，
it was built on top of a technology
它建立在一项技术之上
called Gans which is a really
叫做甘斯
interesting groovy library which makes
有趣的groovy库
it easy to interact with the ants build
与蚂蚁互动很容易
tool in some of its supporting
工具的一些支持
supporting libraries and api's so Gans
支持库和API的So Gans
was technology that we built a build
是我们建造的技术
system on top of for grows one and two
之上的系统增长一和二
and the build system was was was
而构建系统原为
flexible we provided extension points so
灵活，我们提供了扩展点，因此
plugins could participate in the build
插件可以参与构建
system applications could contribute
系统应用程序可以做出贡献
things to the build process so we had a
东西到构建过程中，所以我们有一个
somewhat featural flexible extensible
可以灵活地扩展
build system for girls 1 &amp; 2 but what we
建立女孩1和2的系统，但是我们
did not have was a fully robust really
没有一个完全强大的
complete
完成
flexible build system we didn't set out
我们没有列出的灵活构建系统
to Saul
去扫罗
that problem or we're focused on
这个问题，或者我们专注于
building the web framework and we built
建立网络框架，我们建立了
enough of a build tool to support that
足够的构建工具来支持
the Gradle guys have done just a super
Gradle的家伙做的超级好
fantastic job of building this really
建造这个真的很棒
really robust extensible full-featured
真正强大的可扩展全功能
build system that's much more capable
建立功能更强大的系统
than the build system that we'd built
比我们构建的构建系统
for rails wanting to so one of the
对于想要如此的铁轨之一
changes that we made in girls 3 is we
我们对女孩3所做的改变是
removed the whole build system from from
从中删除了整个构建系统
Grails - and replaced it with Gradle
Grails-并替换为Gradle
integration and that offers a whole
集成，并提供一个整体
bunch of benefits one we have this
一堆的好处，我们有这个
really robust and extensible build
真正强大且可扩展的构建
system now it has much more capability
系统现在具有更多功能
than our lightweight build system had
比我们的轻量级构建系统
another is that the fact that every
另一个事实是，每个
Grails 3 application is built with
Grails 3应用程序内置
Gradle allows us to eliminate a whole
Gradle让我们消除了整体
bunch of stuff that relates to build
一堆与构建有关的东西
time plugin so for example in rails 2
时间插件，例如在Rails 2中
there are plugins for technologies like
有一些技术插件
cobertura and code mark and these are
cobertura和代码标记，这些是
both build time technologies so code
两者都建立时间技术，所以代码
mark is a tool that will do a static
标记是一种将静态
analysis of your source code and report
分析您的源代码和报告
suspicious things or things that you
可疑的事情或你的事情
might consider violations of how you
可能会考虑违反您的方式
want your code put together but it's
希望将您的代码放在一起，但是
doing all that at Build time and
在构建时进行所有操作，
cobertura is a technology for for
cobertura是一项用于
tracking code coverage so you can run
跟踪代码覆盖率，以便您可以运行
your your tests and then the Corporal
您的测试，然后下士
reports will tell you which parts of
报告会告诉您
your system were covered by tests which
您的系统被测试覆盖
work so we have plug-ins for those
工作，所以我们有那些插件
things in browse to Rails plugins for
浏览到Rails插件中
those things and we do not have R is 3
这些东西，我们没有R是3
plug-ins for those technologies because
这些技术的插件，因为
we don't need them because we replace
我们不需要它们，因为我们替换了
our build system with Gradle instead of
我们用Gradle构建系统，而不是
needing a custom Grails plugin for those
需要那些的自定义Grails插件
build time technologies you can use
建立可以使用的时间技术
Gradle plugin fiddle States which just
摇篮插件小提琴国只是
broadens the the kind of landscape of
拓宽了景观的种类
the possibilities all the plugins that
所有插件的可能性
exist out there for Gradle you can use
存在于您可以使用的Gradle中
those rails 3d so that that's just one
那些轨道3d，所以那只是一个
of the list of benefits that we get from
我们从中得到的好处清单
moving the Gradle another has to do with
移动摇篮另一个与
IP integration and I'm going to
IP集成，我要
demonstrate some of this in just a few
仅在少数几个例子中展示一些
minutes so I'm going to jump into an IDE
分钟，所以我要进入一个IDE
and demonstrate some things that might
并展示一些可能
not be obvious but in order for an IDE
并不明显，但是为了使用IDE
to be able to
有能力去
work effectively with a Braille street
与盲文街有效合作
project the IDE does not necessarily
项目IDE不一定
need to have explicit rails 3 support if
如果需要，需要明确的rails 3支持
the IE has really great great little
IE的确很棒
support which IntelliJ IDEA does that
支持哪个IntelliJ IDEA可以做到这一点
that covers a whole lot of ground and
涵盖了很多领域，
gets you to a point where you can be
使您达到可以成为自己的地步
productive building and developing and
生产建设和发展
debugging support rails 3 applications
调试支持Rails 3应用程序
in the item so one of the big
在项目中，所以大之一
differences between one of the
其中之一之间的差异
differences between intelligence
智力之间的差异
community edition and the Ultimate
社区版和终极版
Edition is the Grails three support and
版是Grails的三大支持和
the Grails three support only exists in
Grails的三个支持仅存在于
the Ultimate Edition it specifically
最终版特别
it's not in the community Edition and
它不在社区版中，
that's created some confusion people
这造成了一些混乱的人
routinely will report you cannot do
通常会报告您无法执行
grocery development in IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中的杂货店开发
Community Edition and that's that's not
社区版，那不是
the case you can in fact and I'll
如果你可以的话，我会
demonstrate some of that and Gradle is a
展示其中的一些，Gradle是一个
big part of that so I'll come back to
很大一部分，所以我会回到
that momentarily when we get into the
那一瞬间，当我们进入
IDE but that turns out to be a really
IDE，但事实证明这是一个真正的
big deal for for our users another thing
对我们的用户而言，大不了的另一件事
that changed significantly between rows
行之间的变化很大
2 and rails 3 is we in Grails 3 we've
2和rails 3是我们在Grails 3中
embraced a tree based solution for a lot
拥抱了很多基于树的解决方案
of things that used to be done at run
在运行时要做的事情
time and I'll go into that just a little
时间，我会讲一点
bit and we'll open will see some of this
一点，我们将打开将看到一些
manifest in the IDE in just a little bit
一点点地显示在IDE中
so if Grails developers are familiar
所以如果Grails开发人员很熟悉
with the fact that the framework adds a
该框架添加了一个
whole bunch of capability to classes
上课的全部能力
that you write so for example in a
你这样写，例如
Grails application when you offer a
当您提供Grails应用程序时
domain class so in the main class is a
域类，所以在主类中是
class that represents something you're
代表你的东西的类
going to persist in the database so in a
将要保留在数据库中，所以在
Grails application when you offer a
当您提供Grails应用程序时
domain class there's typically what you
域类通常就是你
would do is you would write the class
你要做的就是写课
and declare the persistent properties in
并在中声明持久属性
the class so if you're writing a person
上课，所以如果你在写一个人
class the person might have a person in
这个人可能有一个人
with a last name in age or whatever it
姓氏或年龄
is that scribes a person and that might
是抄写一个人，并且可能
be all the code that you see in the
是您在
source code for the person class but
人员类的源代码，但是
then a compiled copper at runtime a
然后在运行时编译铜
bunch of capability has been added to
一堆功能已添加到
that class for example there's a method
例如，该类有一个方法
called fake and you can create an
称为假货，您可以创建一个
instance of your domain class and in
域类的实例
both the Save
既保存
method and that will persist the object
方法，它将持久化对象
to the database so you didn't have to
到数据库，因此您不必
write the save method that safe method
写保存方法那安全的方法
is added to your domain class by the
被添加到您的域类中
framework and the save method is just
框架和保存方法只是
one of many many there's lots and lots
许多很多之一
of methods that we add to the main
我们添加到主方法中的方法
classes and all of your other Grails
类和您所有其他的Grails
artifacts like controllers and tag lives
控制器和标签生命之类的工件
and services
和服务
save is just warming table in early
保存只是早期的暖桌
versions of grills so saying Grails warm
烤架的版本，所以说Grails温暖
all of those kinds of things were rigged
所有这些东西都是被操纵的
up at runtime using expandable metaclass
在运行时使用可扩展元类
metaprogramming
元编程
so Berube has capabilities that make it
所以Berube具有使其成为现实的能力
very easy to add behavior to classes at
很容易将行为添加到
runtime while the program is running add
程序运行时运行时添加
methods to classes and Grails did a lot
类和Grails的方法做了很多
of that in grows one as the application
随着应用程序的发展
was starting up we would iterate over
正在启动，我们将迭代
all your Binet classes and dynamically
所有您的Binet类，动态地
add the save method to them and all the
将保存方法添加到他们和所有
other methods that need to be added to
其他需要添加的方法
the game classes so that's that's a
游戏类别，那就是
great set of capabilities and it's the
强大的功能集
fact that Ruby supports that enables
Ruby支持的事实
girls wouldn't even have been possible
女孩甚至不可能
or wouldn't have made sense if we didn't
否则我们就没有意义了
have those kinds get votes but that
有那些获得选票，但那
flexibility is also somewhat expensive
灵活性也有些昂贵
using runtime metaprogramming like that
使用像这样的运行时元编程
is extensive in terms of performance and
在性能方面是广泛的
it's also expensive in terms of memory
在内存方面也很昂贵
consumption always meta methods take up
消耗总是元方法占用
space and even so there are costs
空间，甚至有成本
associated with that in grils - we
与女孩相关联-我们
started moving away from that runtime
开始远离该运行时
meta programming and transition to
元编程并过渡到
compiler meta program where we're able
我们能够编译的元程序
to add these things to your classes at
将这些东西添加到您的班级
compile time and in order to do that the
编译时间，为了做到这一点
framework had to build its own internal
框架必须建立自己的内部
contraption that as an application
作为一种应用
developer you never had interact well
开发人员，您从来没有很好的互动
but it was part of the core of the
但这是
framework and it was kind of our own
框架，这是我们自己的
handmade trait like system where we
像系统一样的手工特质
could add behavior to classes at compile
可以在编译时向类添加行为
time in Brill's 3 what we've done is
在Brill的3中，我们要做的是
eliminated almost all of that and moved
消除了几乎所有这些并搬走了
to a trait basic solution so groovy
特质的基本解决方案
recent versions of groovy have support
groovy的最新版本有支持
for trade and a trait is like a class
贸易和特质就像一个阶级
but unlike classes so Ruby and Java are
但是与类不同的是，Ruby和Java是
both single inheritance languages right
两种单一继承语言都对
so when you author a class in groovy you
所以当您在groovy中编写类时
you have exactly one parent class you
你只有一个家长班
cannot there's no such thing as multiple
不可能没有多重
in here
在这里
so you cannot extend from multiple
所以你不能从多个扩展
classes but you can implement multiple
类，但您可以实现多个
trees and a tree is a lot like a class
一棵树很像一堂课
you author a tracing it has methods and
您编写的跟踪具有方法和
fields and properties and then that tree
字段和属性，然后是那棵树
a class can implement that trait and all
一个班级可以实现这一特质
that behavior becomes part of that class
该行为成为该类的一部分
and in addition to that the class can
除此之外，该类还可以
implement any number of traits so it's
实现任何数量的特征
kind of like multiple inheritance where
有点像多重继承
you can get behavior from a lot of
你可以从很多方面得到行为
different traits add into your class the
不同的特征添加到您的班级
way the girls three embraces that is
女孩三个拥抱的方式是
that when you offer a domain class again
当您再次提供域类时
as an example you don't have to express
例如，您不必表达
that the main class implements any trait
主类实现任何特征
the framework does that for you how that
该框架为您做到了
relates to the IDE is because all of
与IDE相关的原因是因为所有
that behavior is being added to your
该行为被添加到您的
classes at compile time in the form of
类在编译时以以下形式
traits you get really great support from
的特质得到了您的大力支持
the OEE
OEE
for things like auto completion and step
用于自动完成和逐步操作
debugging you can step right into
调试您可以直接进入
methods that aren't even in your source
源代码中甚至没有的方法
code so for example in controller when
代码，例如在控制器中
you invoke that respond method if you're
您可以调用该响应方法
in debug mode you can step into the
在调试模式下，您可以进入
respond method and then which will be
响应方法，然后将
stepping into is the trait and you can
进入是特质，你可以
debug what's going on and that's all
调试发生了什么，仅此而已
just so much easier to deal with than
比处理起来容易得多
trying to debug and understand what I
试图调试并了解我
was going on at runtime when runtime
在运行时正在运行
metaprogramming scorelines supposed to
元编程得分线应该
compile time that burger so again that
再次编译该汉堡的时间
relates to the support that the ide can
与思想所能提供的支持有关
offer for doing Grails 3 development
提供做Grails 3开发
that is a significant improvement over
这是对
what we were able to do with rails rails
我们能用rails rails做些什么
1 and 2 so that's all sort of some ideas
1和2所以有些想法
at the somewhat high level and what I
在较高的水平上，我
want to do is jump into the IDE and
要做的就是跳到IDE中
demonstrates demonstrate a couple of
展示了几个
things what I'm going to do is I'm going
我要去做的事情是
to start with the community edition of
从社区版开始
IntelliJ here so we're working with an
IntelliJ在这里，所以我们正在与
edition of intelligent that does not
没有的智能版
have Grails 3 supported and what I'm
有Grails 3支持，我是什么
going to do is I'm going to open a
我要做的是打开一个
project a Grails 3 project and so by the
项目Grails 3项目，因此
way with the process that I did there is
我在那里做的过程
might be different than what grills 1
可能不同于烤架1
and 2 developers are used to doing so I
和2个开发人员已经习惯了
don't want to create a new project from
不想从创建新项目
the Christian sources
基督教的资料
I don't want to import a project what I
我不想导入项目
want to do is open the project and
想做的就是打开项目，
select the directory that is the parent
选择作为父目录
directory the top-level directory of
目录的顶级目录
your rails 3 project and you should see
您的rails 3项目，您应该看到
a dialog like this and this is the IDE
这样的对话框，这就是IDE
recognizing that this is a Gradle
认识到这是一个摇篮
project and that's going to enable a
项目，这将使
whole bunch of capabilities that that
整个功能
will be able to take advantage of so an
将能够利用这样的优势
important part of this dialog right here
此对话框的重要部分就在这里
is the radio button that says use the
是表示使用
default Gradle wrapper you want to make
您要制作的默认Gradle包装器
sure that is that is configure and if
确保这是配置，如果
you do that you don't have to configure
您无需配置
a Gradle home there's a place down here
一个摇篮屋，这里有个地方
where you could configure a great a home
在这里您可以配置一个好的家
I am the case that you don't do that a
我的情况是你不这样做
better idea is for you to use the Gradle
更好的主意是让您使用Gradle
wrapper that's in the project that
项目中的包装
Grayling wrapper since it's part of the
Grayling包装器，因为它是
project is using a version of Gradle
项目正在使用Gradle版本
that is known to work with that version
已知可以使用该版本
of rails and that version of this
和这个版本的
application and as you're switching back
应用程序，当您切换回去时
and forth between Grails projects you
在Grails项目之间来回
don't want to have to switch to
不想切换到
different versions of Gradle if you're
如果您是不同版本的Gradle
using the wrapper that's part of the
使用包装的一部分
Grails project and whatever project
Grails项目以及其他任何项目
you're working on the be using its
你正在使用它的
wrapper and that will have an inversion
包装器，这将有一个反转
that's appropriate for that project so
那适合那个项目，所以
having this radio buttons like it says
像这样说这个单选按钮
use default Gradle wrapper is an
使用默认的Gradle包装器是
important step and intelligent guys to
重要的一步和聪明的人
fall back on just because that makes
仅仅因为那
sense as a reasonable default so the IDE
合理的默认值，因此IDE
has all been at the Grails project and
都参加过Grails项目，
remember we're in the community edition
记住我们在社区版中
of intelligent here the community
社区的智慧
edition does not have grocery support
版本没有杂货店支持
but we're going to be able to do a
但我们将能够
considerable amounts of development work
大量的开发工作
with the community edition without
没有社区版
grocery support so this directory
杂货店支持，所以此目录
structure here should look familiar to
这里的结构应该看起来很熟悉
several developers you've got Grails -
您有Grails的几个开发人员-
app and below that we've got directories
应用程序及其下的目录
like controllers and knit and if we had
像控制器和编织物，如果我们有
services to services directory we had
服务到我们拥有的服务目录
domain classes you'd have a contained
您将包含的域类
directory but notice that those
目录，但请注意那些
directories don't exist here and that
目录在这里不存在
that relates to something that I want to
与我想要的东西有关
point out that's sometimes a point of
指出有时候
confusion for quotes so the project that
混淆报价，以便该项目
I just opened is in git it's a gift
我刚打开的是git这是礼物
repository and
储存库和
one of the one of the things about get
关于获得的东西之一
is gif does not support storing empty
是gif不支持存储为空
directories so when you create a
目录，所以当您创建一个
brand-new Grails application typically
全新的Grails应用程序通常
the domain directory will be there over
域目录将在那
in SAP as will the services directory in
在SAP中，服务目录在
the tag web directory all those
标签网页目录
directories will be there so if you open
目录将在那里，所以如果您打开
the project in the IDE piee conspires
IDE piee中的项目合谋
with Gradle to figure out what your
与Gradle找出您的
source directories are and the domain
源目录是和域
and services folders would be configured
和服务文件夹将被配置
as source string it's just like the
作为源字符串，就像
controllers folder if you can know if
控制器文件夹，如果你知道
you can tell in the player or not but
你可以告诉玩家，但是
the folder right there is blue as
右边的文件夹是蓝色的
opposed to some of the others that are
反对其他一些
grey and the fact that that's blue
灰色和蓝色的事实
indicates that that's a source directory
表示这是一个源目录
and the IDE was able to figure out that
并且IDE能够弄清楚
this is a source directory because it
这是一个源目录，因为它
reached out to Gradle to say to ask it
伸出手向Gradle询问
hey where's all the sources for this
嘿，这的所有来源在哪里
project and we've got integration built
项目，我们已经建立了集成
into the so Grails and Gradle are
进入Grails和Gradle
conspiring to so when you ask Gradle
当您问Gradle时，共谋
what are the source directory Gradle
什么是Gradle的源目录
notice that this controllers folder is a
请注意，此控制器文件夹是一个
source directory if I were to so I'm
源目录，如果我要的话
going to start up the Grails console
将启动Grails控制台
later so I'm going to open up the
稍后，我将打开
terminal and I'm just like real W which
终端，我就像真正的W
is the grilles wrapper not the Gradle
是格栅包装而不是Gradle
wrapper but the rails wrapper and what
包装，但导轨包装和什么
that's going to do is start up an
要做的是启动一个
interactive prompt here where I can type
我可以在此处输入的交互式提示
so if I thought creates - GOM and I
所以如果我以为创造了-我和GOM
press tab we'll get Auto completion here
按标签，我们将在此处获得自动完成
or create the main class and then
或创建主类，然后
specify the name of the donate class
指定捐赠类的名称
that I want to create and that the main
我想创造的主要
class was just created so notice that
类刚刚创建，所以请注意
the domain folder here was just created
域文件夹在这里刚刚创建
and it's gray it's not a source folder
它是灰色的，不是源文件夹
so if I started editing the files in
所以如果我开始编辑文件
that directory I'm going to have some
该目录，我将要一些
problems if I do the try to navigate to
问题，如果我尝试导航到
a class from the IDE the IDE is not
IDE中的类，IDE不是
going to know that the sore spot or that
会知道那个痛处或那个
the files in that directory represent
该目录中的文件表示
classes so bottom line is I need to get
类，所以我需要获得底线
this domain folder configured as a
该域文件夹配置为
source folder and one way to do that is
源文件夹，一种方法是
if I right-click on the folder and
如果我右键单击该文件夹，然后
select mark directory as sources root
选择将目录标记为源根目录
that that would do it that's one way to
那会做到的，这是一种方法
tell the IDE
告诉IDE
that folder is a source folder and you
该文件夹是源文件夹，而您
have to do that in order for the item e2
必须这样做才能使项e2
to be able to be compiled in class that
能够在该类中进行编译
are in the folder but another way to go
在文件夹中，但另一种方式
about that is notice that this pop-up
关于这一点，请注意，该弹出窗口
came up down here and it says the Gradle
来到这里，说摇篮
project needs to be imported if I click
如果单击，则需要导入项目
import changes what will happen is the
导入更改将发生的是
IDE is going to kind of re-evaluate the
IDE将会重新评估
environment it's going to go back to
环境，它会回到
Gradle and say hey what are the current
摇摇晃晃，说嘿，现在是什么
source directories and at that point
源目录，此时
since this domain folder exists it will
由于此域文件夹存在，它将
be configured as a source for earlier
被配置为早期的源
just to clarify when I mentioned that
只是为了澄清当我提到
gif doesn't support tracking empty
gif不支持跟踪为空
folders I mention that because this
我提到的文件夹，因为
scenario that I'm stepping through right
我正在正确执行的方案
now comes up a lot with rails apps or
现在，Rails应用程序或
someone will create the project
有人将创建项目
immediately put it in get and then
立即将其放入get中，然后
someone else checks it out and there's
别人检查出来，有
no domain folder no services folder and
没有域文件夹没有服务文件夹
the first time you created a name class
第一次创建名称类
or service or taggable you have to deal
您必须处理的服务或标签
with this issue so I can click import
这个问题，所以我可以点击导入
changes and that will cause the IDE to
更改，这将导致IDE
reevaluate the environment and one of
重新评估环境，其中之一
the effects of that will be the domain
的影响将是领域
folder will be configured as a source
文件夹将被配置为源
folder in typically I have auto import
文件夹中，通常我会自动导入
enabled so if you click that enable auto
启用，因此，如果您单击该启用自动
import what will happen is anytime the
导入将随时发生
Grails build changes the IDE will
Grails构建更改，IDE将进行更改
recognize that and will automatically
意识到这一点，并会自动
re-import things for you so you may or
为您重新导入东西，以便您可以或
may not want that turned on and yet one
可能不希望打开它，但是
more way a third way to get this folder
获取该文件夹的第三种方法
configured as a source folder is if you
配置为源文件夹是
open the Grails tools view and select
打开Grails工具视图并选择
your top-level project there and click
您的顶级项目，然后单击
the little circle repress thing the same
小圆圈压抑着同样的东西
thing will happen so I just now click
事情会发生的，所以我现在点击
that and the ID is now reaching out the
那和ID现在伸手
Gradle saying hey what's what's the
摇篮说嘿是什么
current state of things what needs to be
事物的当前状态需要是什么
configured as a source folder and I
配置为源文件夹，我
expect a bunch of stuff is happening
期待一堆东西正在发生
other stuff is happening as well and
其他事情也在发生
once once this rebuild down here
一旦一次，这里重建
complete this the domain folder just now
立即完成此域文件夹
turned blue and for business so be aware
变成蓝色并开始营业，因此请注意
that that these artifact holders like
这些神器持有者喜欢
domain and services the ones that might
域和服务可能
not exist when the project is initially
项目最初时不存在
imported in the IDE has to be configured
必须配置在IDE中导入的内容
as source folders and it's a super
作为源文件夹，这是一个超级
simple
简单
to do in fact I practically never even
其实我几乎从来没有做过
have to think about it because I have my
必须考虑一下，因为我有我的
real development very I have that auto
真正的发展，我有那个汽车
import enable and it all just happens
导入启用，这一切都发生了
another place where that same thing same
同一件事相同的另一个地方
kind of thing comes up is so since we're
出现这样的事情是因为我们
using Gradle as our build tool in
使用Gradle作为我们的构建工具
brailles 3 the way you express
盲文3表达方式
dependencies in a brailles 3 project is
盲文3项目中的依赖项是
the same way you would Express the
用相同的方式表达
tendencies in any Gradle project and
任何Gradle项目的发展趋势，以及
that is built a cradle there is this
建了一个摇篮，有这个
dependencies block and this is standard
依赖块，这是标准的
Gradle and mavin kind of syntax for
Gradle和mavin的语法
expressing dependencies if you were to
表达依赖性，如果您要
add a dependency here or change the
在此处添加依赖项或更改
dependency the IDE
依赖IDE
doesn't know about that yet so if you
还不知道，所以如果你
add a dependency on a library and then
在库上添加依赖项，然后
go start editing source code and try to
开始编辑源代码并尝试
use classes in that library the build
使用该库中的类构建
will succeed if you're building from
如果您从
Gradle but the IDE will be confused and
Gradle，但IDE会令人困惑，并且
won't know about those the new library
不会知道那些新图书馆
unless you've enabled auto import or
除非您启用了自动导入功能，否则
after you add a dependency to this build
将依赖项添加到此版本后
that Gradle file come out here and do
那Gradle文件出来这里做
the same thing that mentioned before and
与之前提到的相同
that is till I tell the IDE to refresh
直到我告诉IDE刷新
refresh itself using by clicking this
通过单击来刷新自身
top-level project and clicking refresh
顶级项目，然后单击刷新
and that tells the IDE to go reevaluate
然后告诉IDE重新评估
things so now the new dependencies that
所以现在新的依赖关系
you've added here will be added to the
您在此处添加的内容将添加到
project's class path from the ideas
想法中项目的课堂路径
perspective and then you can start to
角度，然后您可以开始
reference classes that are in whatever
引用类
library Express the dependency on here
图书馆表达对这里的依赖
so be aware that when you're doing rails
所以要注意，当您在做滑轨时
3 development in any IDE anytime you
随时随地在任何IDE中进行3开发
change dependencies or introduce new
更改依赖项或引入新的
source folders like the domain folder
源文件夹（例如域文件夹）
the IDE needs to kind of make another
IDE需要另辟another径
run at setting up the class staff and
运行设置班级人员和
source maps and all the different
源图和所有不同的
techniques I've just described there are
我刚刚描述的技术有
ways you can go about doing that all
你可以去做的所有方式
right now what I want to do is let's say
现在我要说的是
I want to start that council back up I
我想开始那个理事会的备份
shouldn't stop that what I want to do is
不应该停止我想做的是
generate scaffolding or this person
产生脚手架或这个人
class I just create so let's say the
我刚刚创建的课程，所以我们说
person has a first name and last name
人有名字和姓氏
[Applause]
[掌声]
just like that and I want to generate
就像那样，我想产生
some scaffolding for that so when the
为此一些脚手架，所以当
Grails council down here if I type
如果我键入，Grails委员会就在这里
generate and again I get tab completion
生成并再次获得制表符完成
here so I can tap complete that generate
在这里，我可以点击完成生成
all and then if I start typing the name
全部，然后如果我开始输入名称
of a domain class and press tab you also
域类，然后按Tab
get Auto completion there so the council
在那里自动完成
there knows about all of my domain
那里知道我所有的领域
classes knows what's a reasonable thing
上课知道什么是合理的
to pass as a parameter to generate all
作为参数传递以生成所有
so I press that and now the default
所以我按了，现在默认
scaffolding has been generated for that
为此生成了脚手架
for the person class so we go look at
对于人类，我们去看看
our person controller and and notice
我们的人控人并注意
that we didn't have to do anything
我们不必做任何事情
special with the controller's folder to
特殊的控制器的文件夹
set it up as a source path because the
将其设置为源路径，因为
controller's folder was populated when
控制器的文件夹在
the project was initially imported
该项目最初是导入的
because that's where we happen to put
因为那是我们碰巧放的地方
the URL napkins file so the domain
URL餐巾纸文件，因此域
folder did not exist when we initially
最初时文件夹不存在
imported the project's we had to deal
导入了我们必须处理的项目
with it as a source folder the
与它作为源文件夹
controllers folder did exist when we
当我们
import the project's adapter so in the
导入项目的适配器，以便在
ID I can i can add break points and for
我可以给我添加ID的断点
the most part the debugger is going to
调试器大部分将用于
work here just like it Java developers
就像在这里一样工作Java开发人员
are used to it working one a significant
习惯了
thing that changed in Grails 3 thats
在Grails 3中改变的东西
related to debugging and just running
与调试和运行有关
the application in the IDE in general a
一般情况下，IDE中的应用程序
significant thing that changed is
重大的改变是
remember that in Grails one and two we
记住，在Grails一和二中
had our own build system so in order to
有我们自己的构建系统，以便
build a system or run run the app or
构建系统或运行运行应用程序或
debug the app or really do anything at
调试应用程序或在以下位置执行任何操作
all with the application the IE had to
IE必须具备的所有应用程序
do one of two things it either had to
做两件事之一
shell out a process and effectively type
完善流程并有效输入
Grails space and then some command on
掠取空间，然后执行一些命令
the command line right the IDE could you
IDE可以在命令行正确显示
shell out a process like that or the ID
掏出类似的进程或ID
he could make calls into our build
他可以打电话给我们的建筑
system through through an API but the
系统通过API，但是
IDE had to have to specifically know
IDE必须特别知道
about Grails
关于Grails
in order to do either of those things
为了做任何一件事情
and that's not the case with rails 3
这不是Rails 3的情况
again remember we're in the Ultimate
再次记得我们在终极
Edition
版
I'm sorry wearing the community edition
对不起，穿着社区版
of intelligent that does not have
没有的智能
grocery support in gross three we've
总共有三家杂货店支持
added the ability to run the Grails
增加了运行Grails的功能
application by a standard public static
由标准公共机构申请
void main method so every Java IDE knows
void main方法，因此每个Java IDE都知道
how to run a class that has a main
如何运行一个有主
method so if i just right-clicked in
方法，所以如果我只是右击
this editor and i'm going to run the
这个编辑器，我要运行
application and the as far as the ide is
应用程序和尽可能的想法
concerned all that's happening is it's
担心发生的一切是
just invoking this main method it's not
只是调用这个主要方法而已
starting up Tomcat or doing anything
启动Tomcat或执行任何操作
grylls
格里尔斯
right all it's doing is executing this
正确的是执行此操作
main method just like any other standard
就像其他标准一样
standard main method in a java program
Java程序中的标准main方法
and the effects of doing that is right
这样做的效果是正确的
now Tomcat is things started up the
现在Tomcat已启动
application is being built and deployed
正在构建和部署应用程序
to that Tomcat all of that happens just
到Tomcat，所有这些都发生了
by running the main method in this class
通过运行此类中的main方法
which makes it much much easier for for
这使得它更容易
the application to be run from from the
从中运行应用程序
IDE so again we can get the application
IDE，所以我们可以再次获得该应用程序
running without any support from the IDE
在没有任何IDE支持的情况下运行
me at all or at least any grilled
我，或者至少有我烤
specific support so I've stopped the app
具体的支持，所以我已经停止了该应用程序
there
那里
so when I when I ran the application
所以当我运行应用程序时
this application run configuration was
此应用程序运行配置为
created right in John IntelliJ
是在John IntelliJ中创建的
developers will be or users will be
开发人员将成为或用户将成为
familiar with this this is kind of two
熟悉这是两种
standard stuff there's nothing Brizzy
标准的东西什么都没有
about this this is a specify the class
关于这个，这是一个指定的类
it has a main method in it and the IDE
它有一个主要方法和IDE
knows what to do with that so once that
知道该怎么做，一旦
run configuration is created one way to
创建运行配置的一种方法是
run the app from this point is I can
从这一点运行应用程序是我可以
click the green arrow to run the
点击绿色箭头以运行
application or I can click the green bug
应用程序，或者我可以单击绿色的bug
to run the application in debug mode and
以调试模式运行该应用程序
that's what I've just done and we've got
这就是我刚刚做的，我们已经
a breakpoint in this person controller
此人控制器中的断点
so the debugging agent has started see
因此调试代理已开始查看
that represented in the console there as
在控制台中表示为
soon as Tomcats up and running I can
一旦Tomcats启动并运行，我就可以
send a request to the application and
向应用发送请求
we'll be able to hit this breakpoint and
我们将能够达到这个断点，
debug the application largely like you
像您一样调试应用程序
could any JVM app in in IntelliJ so go
可以在IntelliJ中使用任何JVM应用程序吗
we're interacting with the default
我们正在与默认
scaffolding I just hit this breakpoint
脚手架我刚打到这个断点
and to do
和做
the same stuff that you would expect to
您期望的相同的东西
be able to do in a step debugger here so
能够在这里进行一步调试器
I can interrogate this controller and
我可以询问这个控制器
see all the properties that are in the
查看所有的属性
controller and even though none of these
控制器，即使这些都不是
properties have corresponding source
属性有相应的来源
code entries this is all stuff that's
代码条目这就是所有的东西
been added to your controller by the
被添加到您的控制器
framework even though the IDE doesn't
框架，即使IDE不支持
know anything at all about Grails here
这里对Grails一无所知
it's able to inspect and discover all of
它能够检查和发现所有
these properties that are in this class
此类中的这些属性
because all those properties have been
因为所有这些属性
added to the bytecode at compile time
在编译时添加到字节码
bye-bye Grails this is very different
再见Grails，这是非常不同的
than what you would see say in an Grylls
比您在Grylls中看到的要多
one where everything was being added
一处正在添加所有内容的地方
dynamically at runtime you wouldn't be
在运行时动态地
able to inspect these these problems
能够检查这些问题
because the ID wouldn't know how to even
因为ID甚至不知道如何
discover that they existed so you get a
发现它们存在，所以您得到了
really really great support for running
真的非常支持跑步
the application debugging the
应用程序调试
application and you can run unit tests
应用程序，您可以运行单元测试
you can do most of what you can because
您可以做大部分事情，因为
you cover a whole lot of ground in the
您覆盖了很多领域
community addition of an intelligent
社区增​​加了智能
without any growth specific tool there's
没有任何特定的增长工具
some things you're not going to get so
有些事情你不会得到的
you're not going to get like a GSP
您不会像GSP一样
editor with auto-completion you're not
具有自动补全功能的编辑器
going to get anything real specific but
将获得任何真正的具体但
the application absolutely can be built
该应用程序绝对可以构建
to run debug run your tests so there was
运行调试运行测试，所以有
that there was a period of several
有一段时期
months after we released rails 3 before
在发布Rails 3之前几个月
the first version of intelligent was
智能的第一个版本是
released that included Grails three
发布了包括Grails的三个
support and during those months I used
支持，在过去的几个月里
the community edition of IntelliJ every
每个IntelliJ社区版
single day and was completely productive
一天，完全有生产力
and it was it's just a fine environment
那是一个很好的环境
for doing rails 3 development even
甚至进行Rails 3开发
without the rails 3 support the Grails 3
没有护栏3支撑Grails 3
support in the Ultimate Edition is even
最终版的支持甚至
better you get a bunch of Braille
更好的是你得到一堆盲文
specific support you get like a JSP
您获得像JSP一样的特定支持
editor you get wizards for creating
编辑器，您将获得用于创建的向导
artifacts so or you can right click and
因此，您可以右键单击并
say create a new controller write a new
说创建一个新的控制器写一个新的
to make class that sort of thing you get
让课堂上你得到那种东西
a visual representation of a
的视觉表示
relationship between your domain classes
域类之间的关系
you get real specific stuff out of the
你从中得到真正的具体东西
Ultimate Edition don't get from the
终极版不能从
communities issue
社区问题
you also get things like I cants so
你也会得到像我这样的东西
notice that this word respond it's
注意这个词回应了
easier to see maybe online set
更容易看到也许在线设置
team on the word respond is underlined
下划线的团队强调
and that's the IDE telling you hey I'm
这就是IDE告诉你，嘿，我
not sure this is a valid method call or
不确定这是一个有效的方法调用或
not right Rivi allows supports dynamic
不正确Rivi允许支持动态
dispatch you can call methods that don't
分派您可以调用不
exist so the fact that the IDE doesn't
存在，所以IDE不存在
know that that's a valid method call
知道那是一个有效的方法调用
doesn't make it invalid code the code
不会使它成为无效代码
still compiles and works as it should
仍然可以按需编译和工作
but the idea is is suggesting hey I
但是这个想法是在暗示我
don't know if that's a valid method
不知道那是不是有效的方法
color it is but yeah ye can't verify
颜色是，但是是的，您无法验证
that the same with this called the
与此相同的称为
person counts and this reference to
人员计数，此引用
params so those black underlined items
参数，使那些带有黑色下划线的项目
there are things that the ie can't that
有些事情，即不能
doesn't know about so that that's why
不知道所以这就是为什么
they underlined that is black there what
他们强调说那里是黑色的
I want to do now is I want to get out of
我现在想做的是我想摆脱
the community edition and we're going to
社区版，我们将
jump into the Ultimate Edition and
跳进Ultimate Edition并
demonstrate a couple of things but one
展示几件事，但其中一件
of the things I want to be clear about
我想弄清楚的事情
is is that absolutely you can do Grails
是绝对可以做Grails
3 development in the community edition
3社区版开发
of IntelliJ and be very very productive
IntelliJ并非常有生产力
there are things that are missing all
有些东西全都错过了
the girls specific stuff and the other
这些女孩的具体东西和其他
other items that I just now mentioned
我刚才提到的其他项目
but absolutely can be can be made to
但绝对可以做到
work so what I want to do right now is
工作，所以我现在想做的是
I'm going to check a Grails 3 project
我要检查一个Grails 3项目
out from our github repository and
从我们的github存储库中取出
that's so I want to import this the
那就是我要导入的
semicolon a remote gift repositories
分号远程礼品存储库
we're doing here again we're not taking
我们再次在这里做，我们不接受
advantage of any Grail specific
任何圣杯的优势
capability or missus capabilities that
能力或错过能力
the IDE
IDE
has so Amy knows how to pull in a
所以艾米知道如何拉
project from from a gift repository
礼物库中的项目
knows how to deal with with Gradle the
知道如何处理Gradle
ie just recognize that this project is
即只要知道这个项目是
in fact a Gradle project so I can open
实际上是Gradle项目，所以我可以打开
it and all the stuff that we just saw in
它以及我们刚刚看到的所有内容
the community edition will also happen
社区版也将发生
here in the Ultimate Edition and I'm
在终极版中，我
going to demonstrate some additional
将演示一些其他
capabilities to get you stuff
为您提供东西的能力
alright so the IDE is a deal
好的，所以IDE很划算
with Gradle right now to figure out what
现在与Gradle找出什么
kind of project this is what what are
什么样的项目，这是什么
the source directories what the pennant
源目录的信号旗
piece does this project have the
这个项目有没有
dependencies are important of course to
依赖当然很重要
be added to the IDE s class path and
被添加到IDE的类路径并
once the the import is complete so now
一旦导入完成，现在
we're in a very similar shape that we
我们的状态与我们非常相似
were in the community so again notice
在社区，所以再次注意
there's no the main folder this project
该项目没有主文件夹
doesn't happen to have any domain
恰好没有任何域
classes or tag lids so if we create the
类或标签盖，所以如果我们创建
main classes or tablets we'd have the
主要课程或平板电脑，我们将
same issues here that we have the
同样的问题，我们有
Community Edition that is what we'd have
这就是我们需要的社区版
to tell the IDE that those folders are
告诉IDE这些文件夹是
our shorts this particular project has
我们这个项目的短裤
has a simple unit test in it that's
有一个简单的单元测试，那就是
going to allow me to but I want to use
将允许我但我想使用
to point out a couple of things that
指出几件事
that are simple but are important to
简单但对
know if you're doing Grails development
知道你是否在做Grails开发
in maie so just like you can run the
在湄，所以就像你可以运行
application or debug the application
应用程序或调试应用程序
without any Grails specific interactions
没有任何Grails特定的交互
from the IDE
从IDE
the same is true with with unit tests so
单元测试也是如此，因此
if I right-click in this unit test and
如果我在此单元测试中单击鼠标右键，
select run the unit tests will run and
选择运行，单元测试将运行并
the first time you run the first test in
第一次运行第一次测试
the projects and building has to happen
项目和建筑必须进行
so that this this first test run will
这样，这是第一次测试
take longer than any subsequent test
比任何后续测试花费更长的时间
round but once everything is built then
圆，但一旦一切都建立了
we'll be able to rerun the tests more
我们将能够重新运行测试
quickly and by the way so some I'm
顺便说一句，我有些
trying to not use keyboard shortcuts
尝试不使用键盘快捷键
here so you can see what I'm doing by
在这里，你可以看到我在做什么
right clicking and clicking menus my own
右键单击并单击我自己的菜单
preference is I'm more productive using
偏好是我使用起来更有效率
keyboard shortcuts for all this kind of
这类键盘快捷键
stuff so you can see there in the menu
东西，所以你可以在菜单中看到
that keyboard shortcuts to run a test is
进行测试的键盘快捷键是
a control shift are and that's how I
控制转移是，这就是我的方式
would typically run running in a test
通常会在测试中运行
I'm using the menu so you can see what's
我正在使用菜单，所以您可以看到
going on one of the great things about
进行一件伟大的事情
IntelliJ is as a lot of folks are like
IntelliJ就像很多人一样
me and that is they prefer to do
我，那是他们喜欢做的
everything that they can want to keep
他们想要保留的一切
work as opposed to using a mouse for me
而不是为我使用鼠标
personally I'm more productive using the
就个人而言，使用
keyboard and everything that I want to
键盘和我想要的一切
do in the IDE I can do with keyboard
在IDE中可以用键盘来完成
shortcuts most of the things have
大多数事物都有捷径
keyboard shortcuts already mapped to
键盘快捷键已映射到
them you can see the keyboard shortcuts
他们可以看到键盘快捷键
next
下一个
lots of these menus and there's a system
这些菜单很多，还有一个系统
in the preferences where you can you can
在您可以的首选项中
map your own arbitrary keyboard
映射自己的任意键盘
shortcuts to almost any capability that
几乎所有功能的捷径
the IDE provides so that's one part only
IDE提供的，所以这只是一部分
one a long list but it's one piece of
一个很长的清单，但这是一个
why I really love IntelliJ and why I'm
为什么我真的爱IntelliJ，为什么我
so productive in intelligence I can
我可以在智能方面多产
configure it to do the things that I
配置它来做我做的事情
want to do and since I'm a keyboard user
想做，因为我是键盘用户
I can nap keyboard shortcuts to
我可以将键盘快捷键
everything that that I do routinely that
我日常所做的一切
just makes it more productive all right
只是让它更有生产力
so this test just ran and the test
所以这个测试就跑了
passed but the test is actually running
通过但测试实际上正在运行
in a state that we don't want it to run
在我们不希望它运行的状态下
it with and I'll clarify with what I
我会用我澄清一下
mean by that so I'm going to add a test
意思是说，所以我要添加一个测试
here that has an expectation that the
在这里，期望
current environment is tests right so
当前的环境是正确的测试，所以
Braille has the notion of environments
盲文系统具有环境概念
that your application can be can be
您的应用程序可以是
running in so for example typically when
例如这样运行
you type rails space run app the
您输入rails space run应用
application runs in development mode
应用程序在开发模式下运行
when you run your tests the application
当您运行测试应用程序时
is supposed to run in test mode and when
应该在测试模式下以及何时
you build a war file or an executable to
您构建战争文件或可执行文件以
our file the application is supposed to
我们的文件应用程序应该
run in production mode and then you can
以生产模式运行，然后您可以
have different data sources configured
配置了不同的数据源
for those different environments you can
对于那些不同的环境，您可以
have blocks of code that behave
有行为的代码块
different you can have different spring
不同，你可以拥有不同的春天
means for different environments a lot
对于不同的环境意味着很多
of things in your application might be
您的应用程序中的某些内容可能是
different based on which can burn your
根据哪个可以燃烧您的
life so when your tests are run the
生活，所以当您运行测试时
current environment should be test I'll
当前的环境应该测试一下
press the keep in turkette here to rerun
在此处按保留在土耳其龟重新运行
this test and what we'll see is that
这个测试，我们将看到的是
test is going to fail because the test
测试将失败，因为测试
is actually not running in the Tusk
实际上不在Tusk中运行
environment we'll see that it's actually
环境，我们将看到它实际上是
running in the development environment
在开发环境中运行
which is a depending on what your
这取决于您的
application is doing might be
应用程序可能正在做
problematic
有问题的
so once that
所以一旦
to test should still pass but the
测试仍然应该通过，但是
assertion on line 12 is what I expect to
我期望第12行上的断言
fail and it did fail right so we
失败了，它的确失败了，所以我们
expected environment that current to be
当前预期的环境
equal to test but instead it was
等于测试，但实际上
developed so one of the nice things
发达所以好东西之一
about the change is one one of the nice
关于更改是不错的选择之一
things about the way the weight grocery
关于杂货店的方式的事情
is put together is the ID you can run
放在一起就是您可以运行的ID
the tests without having to interact
无需交互即可进行测试
with any rails environment stuff and
与任何Rails环境相关的东西
that that's what we're doing but one
那就是我们正在做的，但是
small cost event is when the IDE runs
小型事件是IDE运行时
the test the environment is not set up
测试环境未设置
such that the test will run in the test
这样测试将在测试中运行
environment they're going to run into
他们将要遇到的环境
fellow honey partner and there's a
亲爱的伙伴，还有一个
simple way to fix that and that is in
解决这个问题的简单方法
the run configuration for the task if
任务的运行配置，如果
you set the grill set ENB system
您设置烧烤架ENB系统
property to test that will cause the
要测试的属性会导致
tests to run in the test environment so
测试在测试环境中运行
if I rerun this test the test should
如果我重新运行该测试，该测试应该
pass now but a problem with the approach
现在通过，但是方法有问题
that I just now took is that you might
我刚才讲的是你可能
have lots and lots of tests in your
你有很多测试
project you should have lots and lots of
项目你应该有很多
tests in your project you might have
在您的项目中进行测试
hundreds or thousands of tests and you
数以千计的测试，您
don't want to have to go do that - the
不想去做-
Grails D&amp;B thing in every single one of
每一项中都包含Grails D＆B内容
your run configurations for your tests
您的测试运行配置
so most the test is just pass so there's
所以大多数测试只是通过了所以
a better way to fix this problem so what
解决此问题的更好方法
I did was I added the highlighted text -
我所做的是我添加了突出显示的文本-
the Grails DN b equals test i added that
Grails DN b等于测试，我补充说
to the vm options for this particular
这个特定的vm选项
run configuration for that spec and then
运行该规格的配置，然后
if I wouldn't ran another spec I'd have
如果我不运行其他规范
to do the same thing that's not great so
做一件不好的事情
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是
delete that run configuration what's
删除该运行配置是什么
gone now and in the IDE there is this
现在消失了，在IDE中有这个
list of sort of templates for creating
用于创建的模板种类列表
and running configurations and the best
和运行配置以及最佳
way to explain this is just to jump into
解释这个的方法只是跳进去
it so there's a j-unit run configuration
所以有一个j单元运行配置
template here and however this thing is
模板在这里，但是这个东西是
configured from that point forward every
从那时开始，每个
J unit run configuration that's created
创建的J单元运行配置
will be configured per what's defined
将根据定义进行配置
here so for example if I say girls - env
在这里，例如，如果我说女孩-env
because tasks and I'll set another one
因为任务，我将再设置一个
here
这里
our favorite remark trails that won't
我们最喜欢的备注路线不会
actually be used for anything but I'm
实际用于任何东西，但我
putting it there so we'll see it show up
把它放在那里，我们会看到它出现
someplace else in a moment so what I've
一会儿在其他地方，所以我已经
done is I've edited the default template
完成是我编辑了默认模板
for j-unit run configuration and be
用于j-unit运行配置并
aware that this does not change any of
注意这不会改变任何
your existing configurations which is
您现有的配置是
why I deleted the set configuration a
为什么我删除了设置配置
moment ago I wanted to get rid of that
刚才我想摆脱那个
one then edit this template and now from
然后编辑此模板，现在从
this point forward all of the run
至此，所有运行
configurations the j-unit run
配置j单元运行
configurations that are created will be
创建的配置将是
created with that template so if we go
用该模板创建的，所以如果我们去
look at this that was just created see
看看刚刚创建的这个
these things are both there now so from
这些东西现在都在那里
this point forward every time I run a
我每次跑一个
unit test it will be configured with
单元测试它将配置为
those system properties which is which
那些系统属性是
is what I want so that's a one-time
是我想要的，这是一次
small configuration thing I have to do
我要做的小配置
up front when when I first set up a
当我第一次设置一个
project and then map point forward it's
项目，然后将地图指向前方
in place and I don't have to think about
到位，我不必考虑
that anymore
那个了
so be aware that when you're running
因此请注意，当您跑步时
your tests from the IDE they will run in
您从IDE进行的测试将在其中运行
the development environment unless you
开发环境，除非您
say otherwise the way to say otherwise
说其他话
is to set the Grails DnB system property
设置Grails DnB系统属性
and assign it a value of test and a
并为其分配测试值和一个
simple way to impose that is to edit the
施加的简单方法是编辑
j-unit run configuration thing that's
j-unit运行配置的东西
that I just industry alright so we can
我只是行业还可以，所以我们可以
run this application on any of a number
在多个应用程序上运行该应用程序
of ways we could right click here and
我们可以右键单击此处的方法，然后
run it just like I did in the community
像我在社区中一样运行它
edition run the main method another
编辑本版运行主要方法
thing I could do is I could run it from
我能做的是我可以从
the command line by typing Grails space
在命令行中输入Grails空间
run app I can run it from bradle using
运行应用程序，我可以使用Bradle从运行它
the boot run task so there are several
引导运行任务，所以有几个
ways that I can run the project so I'll
我可以运行项目的方式，所以我会
just run it using Gradle W blueprint if
只需使用Gradle W蓝图运行它，如果
if you prefer to click on stuff rather
如果您更喜欢点击东西
than typing things you can come out here
而不是在这里输入内容
to the Gradle tool window and someplace
到Gradle工具窗口和某个地方
around here is right there is poop run
这里附近有便便
so I could double click on that and
所以我可以双击
that's effectively the same thing is
实际上，同一件事是
happening typed boot run on
发生键入启动在
command line so there are a number of
命令行，所以有很多
ways that the application can can be run
应用程序的运行方式
so use whichever is secure development
所以使用安全开发中的任何一个
mode and what's ever whatever's most
模式，什么才是最重要的
productive for you remember that a way
对您有帮助的方式记得
that I could debug this project is just
我可以调试这个项目只是
like we saw in the Community Edition I
就像我们在社区版中看到的一样
can debug the application right here
可以在这里调试应用程序
once the run configuration is created up
一旦运行配置创建好
here I can click the green bug the
在这里我可以单击绿色的bug
running thing in debug mode and those
在调试模式下运行的东西
are both of those are somewhat obvious
两者都明显吗
to folks who are familiar with working
给熟悉工作的人
in the IDE but another technique one
在IDE中，但另一种技术
that I use frequently that is not as
我经常使用的不是
obvious is once you run the application
很明显是一旦您运行该应用程序
from Gradle using the boot run task one
从Gradle使用启动运行任务一
of the things you can do is specify - -
您可以做的事情是指定--
debug - JVM so that's - debug ash JVM
debug-JVM，因此-debug ash JVM
and what that is going to do is that's
而要做的是
going to tell Gradle to start up the
打算告诉Gradle启动
debugging agent when the application
调试代理何时应用
starts up and that's what what just now
启动，这就是现在
has happened is the debugging agent has
发生了调试代理有
been has been started up and it's
已经开始了
configured to suspend which means right
配置为暂停，表示正确
now the process is blocked and waiting
现在，该过程被阻止并等待
for remote debugger to connect to the
供远程调试器连接到
process and it'll wait I think forever I
过程，它会一直等下去，我想我永远
don't know if there's a timeout but
不知道是否有超时，但是
it'll wait for a very long time so it's
它会等待很长时间，所以
just paused right now the application is
刚刚暂停，现在该应用程序是
never going to start up until we connect
除非我们连接，否则永远不会启动
with multi bugger and this is another
多虫，这是另一个
thing a lot of folks don't know how to
很多人不知道该怎么做的事情
do but IntelliJ has great support for
可以，但是IntelliJ对
creating a remote debugging session so
创建一个远程调试会话，以便
what I want to do is I'm going to create
我想做的就是创建
a new run configuration in the IDE here
IDE中的新运行配置
and the type is called remotes and I
这种类型称为遥控器，而我
think it might be easier for folks to
认为人们可能更容易
kind of discover the best there if it
如果能找到最好的地方
was labeled remote debug I think some
被认为是远程调试
folks don't for sure what that's about
人们不确定那是什么
but so I'm going to create a new remote
但我要创建一个新的遥控器
configuration and I typically call mine
配置，我通常称我为
RGB just for a remote debug just a short
RGB仅用于一小段远程调试
name but you can call the thing anything
名字，但你可以称呼任何东西
you like and almost always these
你喜欢而且几乎总是这些
defaults are going to be what you want
默认值将是您想要的
so I'll click OK there and all this
所以我将在其中单击“确定”
happens so far is we've created a run
到目前为止，我们已经创建了一个运行
configuration called
配置称为
our DV
我们的DV
we haven't started it we've just created
我们还没有开始，我们刚刚创建了
it the process is still down here
它的过程仍然在这里
waiting for us to connect a remote
等待我们连接遥控器
debugger so if like if I select the
调试器，如果我选择
already be run configuration and click
已经运行配置并单击
the bug that just now started up the
刚刚启动的错误
remote debugger in the IDE and that
IDE中的远程调试器
remote debugger has connected to the
远程调试器已连接到
debugging agent that has been activated
已激活的调试代理
in our program and now our program is up
在我们的程序中，现在我们的程序已启动
and running I go out here to photos
和跑步我出去这里拍照
colon 8080 and get out here we can
冒号8080并离开这里，我们可以
search for one of my favorite prog rock
搜索我最喜欢的编曲之一
bands King Crimson and click search
乐队King Crimson并点击搜索
iTunes and a request just now was sent
iTunes和刚才的请求已发送
out to the iTunes Apple Store and these
到iTunes Apple Store以及这些
are all the search results that that
是所有的搜索结果
came out of that I can click on one of
从中我可以点击其中一个
those links and now I'm off into the
这些链接，现在我进入
Apple Store doing whatever the Apple
苹果商店做什么苹果
store allows me to do there but my
商店允许我在那里做，但我的
applications up and running and it's
应用程序启动并运行，
running in debug mode because I started
因为我开始在调试模式下运行
it with - - debug - JVM and I connected
它与--调试-JVM和我连接
a remote debugger so now if I were to
一个远程调试器，所以现在如果我要
come on here and put a breakpoint in my
来这里，在我的身上放一个断点
controller come back to the app and
控制器回到应用程序，
search or initiate another search we
搜索或发起另一个搜索，我们
just hit this breakpoint I can see the
刚打到这个断点，我就能看到
search term I can interrogate the whole
搜索字词，我可以查询整体
state of the world around me at this
我周围的世界状况
point in the program so it's it's super
指向程序，所以它超级好
easy to connect a remote debugger to
易于将远程调试器连接到
your Grails application from the IDE so
您从IDE获得的Grails应用程序
again I'm gonna stop yeah but the steps
再次，我要停止耶，但是步骤
that I use there is when I ran the
当我运行
application from Gradle I include the -
来自Gradle的应用程序，我包括-
- debug - JVM and then I had to connect
-调试-JVM，然后我必须连接
the remote debugger from the IDE just
来自IDE的远程调试器
super simple to do but you only have to
超级简单，但您只需要
do that you only need the remote
这样做，您只需要遥控器
debugger stuff if you're using this
调试器的东西，如果您正在使用此
approach the - people on JVM business if
与JVM业务相关的人员
you were debugging the application by
您正在通过以下方式调试应用程序
using the IDs built-in debug support you
使用ID内置的调试支持您
wouldn't have to among company that it
不必在公司当中
just turns out that as I'm doing
只是证明我在做
development there for various reasons I
我出于各种原因在那里发展
might want to be starting the
可能想开始
application from brittle and
从脆性和
I might also want to be debugging the
我可能还想调试
application so I get to do both of them
应用程序，所以我两个都做
and the ID makes all that really really
而ID确实使所有这些
really easy to do so
真的很容易做到
the intelligent really is a super
聪明的人真的是超级
productive environment for me I've been
我去过的生产环境
using celibate for a very long time I
我长期使用celibate
use it every day the whole team a home
整个团队每天都在使用它
Braille is seen here at LCI uses
盲文可以在LCI使用中看到
IntelliJ every day and it's just by
每天都有IntelliJ
itself kind of it's all it's all alone
本身就是全部
as the very best IDE for for doing
作为最好的IDE
grocery development I really say the
杂货店发展我真的说
same thing for doing JVM development in
在JVM中进行开发同样的事情
general but in particular I spend all my
一般，但特别是我花了我所有的时间
time doing rails work and the thing just
时间做铁轨工作和事情只是
works awesome so maybe some of the
效果很棒，所以也许其中一些
reasons that you might choose put on the
您选择的理由放在
short list of reasons that I think
我认为原因的简短列表
IntelliJ really is the very best IDE for
IntelliJ确实是最好的IDE
doing grocery development one is you've
做杂货开发之一是你
got licensing options right you can use
拥有可以使用的许可选项
the community edition which is open
公开的社区版
source it's free it's a great way to
来源是免费的，这是一种很棒的方式
take the thing out for a spin and see if
把东西拿出来旋转一下，看看是否
you like it you can also use the
您喜欢它，也可以使用
Ultimate Edition for free for 30-days I
终极版可免费使用30天
believe you can download the thing it's
相信你可以下载它的东西
fully operational it's not restricted in
完全可操作，不受限制
any way other than time limit but so
除了时间限制以外的任何方式，但是
you've got options you can use the free
您有选择，可以免费使用
open-source version of the IDE or you
IDE的开源版本或您
can get even more more support from the
可以从
from the Ultimate Edition another reason
最终版的另一个原因
that I saw today really is the very best
我今天看到的真的是最好的
IDE for doing Grails 3 development is
用于进行Grails 3开发的IDE是
the long history that we had to get the
我们必须获得的悠久历史
guys that the folks at JetBrains built
JetBrains的人们建造的人
really really great support for grills
对烤架的支持真的很棒
from the very very beginning really to
从一开始就真的
be honest I believe that they had really
老实说，我相信他们真的
great support for Grails before it might
对Grails的大力支持
have even made sense to do that I was
甚至有道理，我曾经
really impressed and excited and how
真的印象深刻，激动不已
quickly JetBrains
快速JetBrains
got on board and invested significantly
加入并进行重大投资
in building really really great Ruby
在构建真正非常出色的Ruby中
support really great Grails support that
支持非常好的Grails支持
they've just kind of led led the way the
他们只是带领了
entire time we've been at this for
整个时候我们都在
almost a little over 10 years now where
现在差不多十多年了
else existed and for almost that entire
其他存在，几乎整个
time IntelliJ IDEA has had really really
IntelliJ IDEA曾经真的
great Grails got really great Grails one
伟大的Grails真的很棒Grails之一
spork great Grails to support and even
散布伟大的Grails来支持甚至
better for L Street
更适合L街
we've got really great collaboration
我们之间的合作非常好
between the teams so the NATO and the
团队之间，因此北约和
other folks there at get brains who
那里的其他人很聪明
build the the groovy and grails support
建立Groovy和Grails支持
anytime we've got an issue or questions
每当我们有问题或疑问时
or ideas for how to make things better
或如何使事情变得更好的想法
we hear the British team will reach out
我们听说英国队会伸出援手
to those guys they're always super easy
对那些家伙来说，他们总是超级容易
to work with really friendly really
与非常友好的人一起工作
smart productive folks and that's been
聪明的生产者，这已经
an important part of I think it's been
我认为这很重要
an important part of enabling the IDE to
启用IDE的重要部分
have such great support for the
有这么大的支持
framework over the years and the support
多年来的框架和支持
kind of goes in both directions often
经常双向走
the folks at Jeff range will reach out
杰夫（Jeff）系列的人将伸出援手
to us with something that's unclear
对我们来说还不清楚
about how how Grails works internally or
关于Grails在内部如何工作或
something that relates to support
与支持有关的东西
they're building in the IDE the dealer
他们正在IDE中构建经销商
one of the other folks out there will
那里的其他人之一
reach out to us and and we'll work with
与我们联系，我们将与
them because it's an our interest for
他们，因为这是我们的兴趣
them to have really great support as
他们有很大的支持
well so that the collaboration between
好让彼此之间的合作
the teams has always been really really
团队一直非常
great I think we worked work together
太好了，我想我们一起努力
well and the end result is is what you
好，最终结果就是你
see and that is just really really
看，那真的是真的
first-rate support for the Grails
对Grails的一流支持
framework in the IDE it really is the
IDE中的框架确实是
very best Grails three support I don't
最好的Grails三项支持，我不支持
think there's there's any question about
认为有任何问题
that and really all of this stuff really
那个，实际上所有这些东西
boils down to the most important part is
归结为最重要的部分是
is productivity and productivity has
生产力和生产力有
always been a guiding principle in the
一直是
grosgrain we make design decisions for
罗缎我们为
how things are going to work in the
事情将如何进行
framework productivity is always at the
框架生产力始终处于
top of the list how can we make things
列表顶部我们如何制作东西
more productive for the developer
为开发人员提高生产力
developer productivity might be the
开发人员的生产力可能是
single most important factor it's
一个最重要的因素是
certainly on the short list as when we
当然在短名单上，就像我们
implement new features and ideas and
实施新功能和想法，以及
make decisions about how we want things
决定我们想要的东西
to work in the framework and you can
在框架中工作，您可以
tell just from a user's perspective that
仅从用户角度讲
the folks at JetBrains take the exact
JetBrains的员工采取了确切的措施
same approach
同样的方法
it's an idea it's just a super
这是一个超级想法
productive environment for me I like to
我喜欢的生产环境
do everything with a keyboard the IDE
使用键盘可以完成所有操作
allows me to do that really really
允许我真的真的做到这一点
flexible folks who don't like to do that
灵活的人，他们不喜欢那样做
you put you don't have to do that right
你说你不必那样做
there's not just one way to do things
不仅有一种做事的方法
the IDE promote provides options that
IDE升级提供的选项
make that will make the most sense for
使那对于
different options we'll make more sense
不同的选择，我们会更有意义
for different folks productivity is
对于不同的人，生产力是
really key from both of our perspectives
从我们两个角度来看，真正的关键
from the Grails teams perspective and
从Grails团队的角度来看，
from Jeff rains and I think both both
来自Jeff Rains，我认为两者
both teams have done a really really
两个团队都做了非常非常
great job of achieving those goals I use
实现我使用的那些目标的出色工作
as I said before I use IntelliJ IDEA
正如我在使用IntelliJ IDEA之前所说的
every single day and I could not be
每一天，我不能
happier with the productivity
生产率更高
specifically for building Grails
专门用于建造Grails
applications just it couldn't be better
应用程序再好不过了
I've got nothing but nothing to great
我什么都没有，但是什么都没有
things to say about the a well yeah I
关于一口井的事情我是的
think that's it Jeff thank you for
认为就是这样Jeff谢谢你
taking the time and making this
花时间做这个
wonderful presentation and thanks for
精彩的演讲，并感谢
all attendees for for actually doing us
所有实际为我们做的参与者
and again for questions there's a select
再有问题，有一个选择
channel about grills and there's a
关于烤架的频道，有一个
dedicated channel wrong IntelliJ IDEA so
专用通道错误IntelliJ IDEA因此
feel free to ask all the questions
随时问所有问题
unanswered
未回答
today there and Daniel and maybe higher
今天在那里，但以理乃至更高
maybe you in Jeff be happy to to to
也许你在杰夫很高兴
enter and copy definitely fantastic
输入并复制绝对很棒
thanks everyone
感谢大家
stay tuned for more webinars and yep
请继续关注，以获取更多网络研讨会和知识
ever good day
美好的一天